[{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":22507,"timeElapsed":111114},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679383217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":13607,"timeElapsed":124722},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679392266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9048,"timeElapsed":133771},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679396401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4134,"timeElapsed":137906},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679401370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4968,"timeElapsed":142875},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679416241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":14870,"timeElapsed":157746},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679426521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":10279,"timeElapsed":168026},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679436617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":10095,"timeElapsed":178122},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679445145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"226","question":"If you had to train an animal to perform in a circus or other show, what animal would you train and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8527,"timeElapsed":186650},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679463217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":15247,"timeElapsed":204722},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679471185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7967,"timeElapsed":212690},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679481098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9911,"timeElapsed":222602},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679486322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5224,"timeElapsed":227827},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679490689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4366,"timeElapsed":232194},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679501154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":10463,"timeElapsed":242658},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679509449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8295,"timeElapsed":250954},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679516425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":6976,"timeElapsed":257930},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679526505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":10079,"timeElapsed":268010},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679542050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":13672,"timeElapsed":283555},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679549737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7686,"timeElapsed":291242},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679554954,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":5215,"timeElapsed":296459},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679560498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5544,"timeElapsed":302003},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679564674,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":4175,"timeElapsed":306179},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679574233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":9559,"timeElapsed":315738},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679580322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":6088,"timeElapsed":321827},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679593425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":13102,"timeElapsed":334930},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679603257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"172","question":"What is your favorite piece of furniture in your home and where did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":9831,"timeElapsed":344762},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679640626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":35288,"timeElapsed":382130},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679649473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":8847,"timeElapsed":390978},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679664761,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":15288,"timeElapsed":406266},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679668482,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3719,"timeElapsed":409987},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679671761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3278,"timeElapsed":413266},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679676281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4519,"timeElapsed":417786},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679683825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":7544,"timeElapsed":425330},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679694953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":11127,"timeElapsed":436458},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679701833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6879,"timeElapsed":443338},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679711521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":9687,"timeElapsed":453026},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679725513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":12615,"timeElapsed":467018},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679737033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":11520,"timeElapsed":478538},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679742113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5079,"timeElapsed":483618},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679745337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3223,"timeElapsed":486842},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679750265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4927,"timeElapsed":491770},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679756953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6687,"timeElapsed":498458},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679762914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":5960,"timeElapsed":504419},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679768850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5935,"timeElapsed":510354},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679776153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"98","question":"If you had to write your own eulogy to be read at your funeral, what would it say in brief?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":7303,"timeElapsed":517658},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679785777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":8447,"timeElapsed":527282},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679794362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8584,"timeElapsed":535867},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679797561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":539066},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679801969,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":4407,"timeElapsed":543474},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679806345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4375,"timeElapsed":547850},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679812362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":6015,"timeElapsed":553867},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679820473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":8111,"timeElapsed":561978},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679828945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":8471,"timeElapsed":570450},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679836137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7191,"timeElapsed":577642},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679855665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":18519,"timeElapsed":597170},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679862513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":6847,"timeElapsed":604018},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679866505,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3991,"timeElapsed":608010},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679869562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3056,"timeElapsed":611067},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679872521,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2958,"timeElapsed":614026},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679878449,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5927,"timeElapsed":619954},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679883785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5335,"timeElapsed":625290},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679892529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":8743,"timeElapsed":634034},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679898777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"41","question":"If you were given the chance to relive any day in your life, do you know which day it would be? What happened?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6247,"timeElapsed":640282},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679909745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":9799,"timeElapsed":651250},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679915753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6007,"timeElapsed":657258},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679922281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6527,"timeElapsed":663786},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679925073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2791,"timeElapsed":666578},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679928609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":670114},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679949473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":20863,"timeElapsed":690978},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679955833,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":6359,"timeElapsed":697338},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679962033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6199,"timeElapsed":703538},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679978753,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16720,"timeElapsed":720258},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679995321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":16567,"timeElapsed":736826},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680005529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":9399,"timeElapsed":747034},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680012649,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":7120,"timeElapsed":754154},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680018433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":5783,"timeElapsed":759938},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680023322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4888,"timeElapsed":764827},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680027625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4303,"timeElapsed":769130},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680041793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":14167,"timeElapsed":783298},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680049849,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8055,"timeElapsed":791354},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680056921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7071,"timeElapsed":798426},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680062897,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5975,"timeElapsed":804402},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680074225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":10168,"timeElapsed":815730},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680082585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":8359,"timeElapsed":824090},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680087377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4791,"timeElapsed":828882},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680092409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":5031,"timeElapsed":833914},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680096121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3712,"timeElapsed":837626},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680117465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":21343,"timeElapsed":858970},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680122865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5399,"timeElapsed":864370},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680136785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":13919,"timeElapsed":878290},{"subjectID":"0z3znkauv5","prolificID":"558acd52fdf99b65685f03d9","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b46ea9a49a64066377d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680144225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7439,"timeElapsed":885730}]